# ISMAIL BENTABET

Saida, Ain-Elhdjar, DZ| +213 (794) 75-3644 | <u>ismailbentabett@gmail.com</u> github.com/ismailbentabett | <u>linkedin.com/in/ismailbentabett | ismailbentabett.com</u>

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Engineer with six years of experience collaborating in small and large teams to build comprehensive and user-friendly web & mobile applications. A self-motivated and lifelong learner, adept at both frontend and backend development, well-versed in modern web technologies.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Junior Software Engineer, Sig-Service

May 2022 - Oct 2022

- Developed and implemented the SFA-13 CRM, connecting a Vuejs & Capacitor App seamlessly with Odoo API.
  Technologies used include Javascript, Typescript, Vue.js, Cypress, HTML, CSS, and Tailwindcss..
- Successfully integrated diverse modules into the company's app, optimizing Sales, Accounting, Lead, Human Resource, CRM, and Reporting functionalities. Improved overall application performance.

## Software Engineer & Co-founder, Shortcut

Jul 2020 - Nov 2023

- Initiated and drove the development of an Online Work Platform in a small startup, employing Javascript, Typescript,
  Vue.js & Nestjs for streamlined implementation.
- Guided a compact development team, ensuring successful project delivery within 6 mounths, contributing to the startup's initial growth.

### **SKILLS**

Languages: Arabic, French, English

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, C#, PHP, Vuejs, Reactjs, Angular, . Net core, Laravel, Node.

**EDUCATION** 

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science, University of Dr Tahar MOULAY Saida

Jan 2018 - Jun 2022

### **PROJECTS**

# Developer, TRP (trp-france.fr)

Jun 2023- Nov 2023

- Enhanced TRP's backend and frontend features using Laravel 10, Vue 3, and Tailwind CSS. resulting in a more streamlined and user-friendly experience.
- Collaborated on integrating Laravel 10, Vue 3, Inertiajs, and Tailwind CSS, FilamentPHP, for TRP, ensuring a cohesive and visually appealing user interface. Contributed to increased user engagement and positive feedback.

#### Developer, Silikan (github.com/silikan)

Mar 2022- May 2022

- Developed and implemented features for both the backend and frontend of the Silikan project using Laravel 10, Vue 3, and Tailwind CSS. Streamlined the user experience and enhanced the platform's functionality
- Integrated Technologies: Integrated Laravel 10, Vue 3, and Tailwind CSS seamlessly to ensure a cohesive and responsive user interface

## Developer, Screamer(github.com/ismailbentabett/Screamer)

Feb 2023 - Apr 2023

- Developed features for Silikan project, seamlessly integrating Angular and .NET Core with Domain-Driven Design principles.
- Enhanced user experience and functionality using Tailwind CSS for cohesive styling

### **AWARDS AND ACCOLADES**

First Place End Of Studies Project

2022

Startup Label Owner & Startup Founder

2020